pillscioffline.com 2011-10-07

# Canadian Family Pharmacy - Privacy Policy

### General Info

Visiting the Canadian Family Pharmacy web site you are encouraged to carefully read the information provided. This includes certain information about services offered which may have separate privacy and security information.

Canadian Family Pharmacy recognizes the right to confidentiality of every individual who visits our web site and completely maintains this right. This Privacy Policy outlines the information Canadian Family Pharmacy will collect and how that information will be used. It also provides information on the security means which are used to protect that information.

### Personal Information

Canadian Family Pharmacy is dedicated to maintaining all customers privacy. All information collected online is strictly, professionally and exclusively used by the Canadian Family Pharmacy to appropriately care and manage all individuals.

When you visit our web site we will not collect your personal data such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, billing data, telephone number etc. unless you provide it to us voluntarily. We also will never collect any personal information from you revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, or details of health, disability or sexual activity or orientation.

When you order from Canadian Family Pharmacy you have to fill in the form which includes your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date and some other information to complete the ordering process. Canadian Family Pharmacy does not give, rent, loan or sell any of this information to any third party. The personal information that you provide to Canadian Family Pharmacy when ordering products via our web site is used only for identification purposes and serves to assist you to receive your orders quickly and easily.

### Personal Information Security

Canadian Family Pharmacy treats your personal information (including credit card data) with the highest level of security. We use a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Technology. This is the most advanced form of security for transactions over the Internet. It means that when you place an order online your personal information is encrypted using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. It makes it virtually impossible for your credit card details to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted to our server. Your personal information is always stored in encrypted form in a secure database to prevent theft.

The challenge of all web privacy and security codes are constantly changing. Canadian Family Pharmacy will always remain up-to-date with the use of fire walls and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to help insure that your information is protected and private.

Canadian Family Pharmacy limits all staff and employees access to patient information through strict security codes. All staff and employees are oriented to security and privacy policies and are updated regularly. Private password access to various areas of information, purchases and all correspondents is strictly enforced and continuously monitored.

### Secure yourself

Remember to close your browser when you have finished your user session. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or internet cafe. You as an individual are responsible for the security of and access to your own computer.

Be also aware that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information over the internet (for example: in discussion forums, via e-mail, or in chat sites) that this information can be intercepted or collected and used by others.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please, use the [Customer Support Ticket System](http://pillscioffline.com/conatcts/form/) to contact us.
